Good night, Sheldon.
- But how am I going to get to work?
- Take the bus.
But I can't take the bus.
They don't have seat belts.
(Sheldon:)And they won't let you lash yourself
to the seat with bungee cords.
(Leonard:)You tried to lash yourself
to the seat with bungee cords?
(Sheldon:)I didn't try, I succeeded.
But for some reason, it alarmed the other
passengers and I was asked to de-bus.
(Leonard:)Oh, you're a big boy. You'll figure it out.
(Sheldon:)Don't talk to me like I'm a child.
(Sheldon:)Now take me
to return my Star Wars sheets.
(Sheldon:)Penny?
Penny? Penny?
(Penny(opening door):)Sheldon, what is it?
(Sheldon:)Leonard's asleep.
(Penny:)Thanks for the update.
(Sheldon:)No, wait.
(Sheldon:)You have to drive me to work.
Yeah, I really don't think I do.
(Sheldon:)But I don't drive
and I can't take the bus.
(Penny:)You'll be fine as long as
you don't do that bungee thing.
(Scene:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)Didn't you recently state
that you and I are friends?
(Penny:)Yes, Sheldon, we are friends.
(Sheldon:)Then I hereby invoke
what I'm given to understand...
(Sheldon:)...is an integral part
of the implied covenant of friendship.
The favor.
(Penny:)Oh, dear God.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I didn't realize
I was interrupting your morning prayers.
(Sheldon:)When you're done, we'll go.